MOSTAFA MOHAMED

Full Name Mostafa Mohamed Ahmed Fouad

Address Assuit ,Egypt

Email Mostafamohamed19070@gmail.com

Phone 01096717241 **Date of Birth** 15-2-2003

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/mostafa-mohamed-623532202/

OBJECTIVE

I am a senior student at Assuit University with a passion for web development and IT. I want to use my skills and knowledge to contribute to exciting projects and work in a dynamic environment. I have experience as a web developer at Assuit Robotics and as an IT member in Enactus AU. My goal is to bring my expertise to create valuable solutions and grow professionally

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2022-Sep 2022 Traning in Assuit Oil Refining Company

Sep 2021 – present IT member in Enactus AU student activity

Mar 2023 - present Web developer in Assuit Robotic

PROJECTS

- Smsarak
- SkipList
- <u>E-commerce</u>

EDUCATION

Senior Student • Faculty of computer and information • Assuit university

LANGUAGES

C++ - MySql
Java - Sql Server
C# - Backend.NET
Paython - Html5 and css3

- OOP - JS

Data StructuresMachine learning